(Leonard:)It's hard to believe
Howard's having a kid.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Amy:)Penny, you're the one who
introduced him to Bernie.
(Penny:)How many times do I have
to say I'm sorry?
(Leonard:)It's not just Howard
and Bernadette. I mean,
(Leonard:)look how far
we've all come.
(Stuart:)Hmm.
Hmm.
(Stuart:)You two got married.
(Amy:)Sheldon and I
are living together.
(Sheldon:)But if my mom asks,
we have bunk beds.
(Leonard:)Penny was a struggling
actress when we met,
(Leonard:)and now she's a successful
pharmaceutical rep.
(Penny:)Okay, you don't have to say
“struggling” every time.
You can just say “actress.”
(Stuart:)Howard went to space.
(Amy:)Bernadette got
her doctorate.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, Howard and I are
working with the government
(Leonard:)on our quantum gyroscope.
(Amy:)We've all come a long way.
(Amy:)There's a lot
to be proud of.
(Raj:)For God's sake, just drive in
the knife, why don't you!
(Stuart:)What's your problem?
Well, you're all thinking
that I'm the only one who
hasn't done anything worthwhile.
(Sheldon:)I was not thinking it.
(Sheldon:)Although, now that
you point it out, it is undeniable.